cagewarriors.com 2019-04-30

# PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY

                                PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY
WA (Number 1) Limited (“CW”, “our”, “we”, “us”) takes your right to privacy very
seriously. This Privacy and Cookie policy (“Policy”), aims to give you information on how
CW collects and processes your personal data when you use https://cagewarriors.com
(“Website”).
This Policy was last updated on 14/05/18
     1. Introduction
When you supply any personal data to CW we have legal obligations towards you in the way
that we use that data. We must collect the information fairly and explain to you how we will
use it. This Policy sets out that information for you.
It is important that you read this Policy together with any other privacy notice or fair
processing notice that we may provide at or around the time that we collect or process
personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using that data.
This Policy supplements the other notices and is not intended to override or replace them.
Please note that our Website and any of our services are not intended for children (those
aged 13 and under) and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.
The data protection law in the UK will change on 25 May 2018. Although this Policy sets out
most of your rights under the new laws, we may not yet be able to respond to some of your
requests (for example, a request for the transfer of your personal data) until May 2018 as we
are still working towards getting our systems ready for some of these changes.
For ease of reading, we have divided this Policy into several sections:
     1.  Introduction
     2.  What information do we collect?
     3.  How is your personal data collected?
     4.  How and why do we use/share your information
     5.  How long do we keep your information for?
     6.  Security
     7.  Cookies
     8.  Your Rights
     9.  Contact Details
     2. What information do we collect?
What is personal data?
Where this Policy refers to ‘personal data’ it is referring to data about you (or other living
people) from which you could be identified – such as your name, your date of birth, your
contact details and even your IP address.
By law all organisations in the UK are obliged to process your personal data in certain ways
and to ensure that you are given an appropriate amount of information about how they use
it. You also have various rights to seek information from those organisations about how they
are using your data, and to prevent them from processing it unlawfully. For more information
about these rights, please see the ‘Your Rights’ section of this Policy.
Data we collect from you when you use our Website

Depending on how you interact with us, CW will collect the following from you:
    •   Identity Data: Name
    •   Organisation/Publication Data: Name
    •   Contact Data: E-mail address
    •   Technical Data: includes IP address, login data, browser type and version, time
        zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and
        platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website.
    •   Usage Data: includes information about how you use our Website, products and
        services.
    •   Marketing and Communications Data: includes your preferences in receiving
        marketing from us.
We also collect, use and share Aggregated Data such as statistical or demographic data for
any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your personal data but is not
considered personal data in law as this data does not directly or indirectly reveal your
identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of
users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated
Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the
combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this Policy.
Updating your information
If you want to update the information you have previously given to us (e.g. if you have
recently moved office or changed your email address), you can contact CW at:
info@cagewarriors.com..
    3. How is your personal data collected?
We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:
     • Direct interactions. You may give us your Identity and Contact Data by filling in
         forms or by corresponding with us by e-mail. This includes personal data you
         provide when you:
             o submit a form on our contact page;
             o provide details in a press application form; and
             o provide your details to receive offers and updates and other marketing
                  material from us.
     • Automated technologies or interaction. As you interact with our Website, we may
         automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and
         patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies and other similar
         technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other
         websites employing our cookies. Please see the section on cookies for further
         details.
     • Third parties. We may receive personal data about you from various third parties as
         set out below:

             o Technical Data from analytical providers, such as Google based outside the
                 EU.
     4. How and why do we use/share your information
Collecting your information
Here are some examples about how we may use the information we collect about you, to:
     •  Communicate with you about events and services of CW, e.g. by responding to
        enquiries or requests;
      • Administer this Website
      • Customise the service we provide to you
      • Handle enquiries submitted to us by you
      • Send you our newsletter and information about products and services that may be of
         interest to you, if you have agreed to us doing so. This may be by email. If at any
         time you do not wish to continue to receive these details then contact us using these
         details: info@cagewarriors.com
For the avoidance of doubt, we will not contact you for promotional purposes, such as
notifying you of new services unless you specifically agree to be contacted for such
purposes at the time you submit your information on the Website, or at a later time if you
sign up specifically to receive such promotional information.
Why is CW allowed to use your information in this way?
CW will only use your personal data in the following circumstances:
     •  Where we need to do so in order to perform a contract we have entered into with
        you.
     •  Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your
        fundamental rights do not override those interests.
     •  Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.
     •  Where we have your consent as a legal basis for processing to send you any direct
        marketing from us or third parties via e-mail. You have the right to withdraw consent
        to marketing at any time by contacting us at info@cagewarriors.com.
Sharing your information
Depending on how and why you provide us with your personal data. We may share it in the
following ways:
     •  We may analyse and disclose aggregated statistics about our Website visitors and
        users of our service in order to describe our services to prospective partners and
        other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will
        include no personally identifying information.
     •  We may disclose personal data if required to do so by law or if we believe that such
        action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of
        the Website or its visitors.

Service Providers
We will use third party service providers to undertake processing operations on our behalf
(for example, MailChimp and Future Ticketing), and this may require us to share your
personal data with them. These service providers provide us with a variety of administrative,
statistical, and technical services. We will only provide service providers with the minimum
amount of personal data they need to fulfil the services we request, and we stipulate that
they protect this information and do not use it for any other purpose. We take these
relationships seriously and oblige all of our data processors to sign contracts with us that
clearly set out their commitment to respecting individual rights, and their commitments to
assisting us to help you exercise your rights as a data subject.
Please note that some of our service providers are based outside of the European Economic
Area (the “EEA”). Where we transfer your data to a service provider that is outside of the
EEA we seek to ensure that appropriate safeguards are in place to make sure that your
personal data is held securely and that your rights as a data subject are upheld. For
example, MailChimp is based in the US and is part of the Privacy Shield which requires them
to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US. For
further details, see European Commission: EU-US Privacy Shield.
Please contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us
when transferring your personal data out of the EEA
Links to third party sites
Please note that where we provide links to third party websites that are not affiliated with CW
such sites are out of our control and are not covered by this Policy, regardless of whether
they use our branding or logo on their websites. If you access third party sites using the links
provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you that could be used by
them, in accordance with their own privacy policies. Please check these policies before you
submit any personal data to these websites.
    5.    How long do we keep your information for?
We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we
collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting
requirements.
To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount,
nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use
or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data
and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal
requirements.
In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see ‘Your Rights’ below for
further information.
    6. Security

CW takes the protection of your information very seriously. We use encryption (SSL) to
protect your personal data when appropriate, and all the information provided to CW is
stored securely once we receive it.
CW may store your personal data on secure servers either on our premises or in secure
third party data centres.
      7. Cookies
A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the
browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are.
A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the
'lifetime' of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.
A cookie can be classified by its lifespan and the domain to which it belongs. By lifespan, a
cookie is either a:
      •  Session cookie. Temporary cookie that remains in the cookie file of your browser
         until you leave the website.
      •  Persistent cookie. This remains in the cookie file of your browser for much longer
         (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).
As for the domain to which it belongs, there are either:
      •  First-party cookies. These cookies are issued from the website you have accessed
         and often serve to give memory about your data and preferences.
      •  Third-party cookies. These are stored by a different domain to the visited page’s
         domain.
Find out more about cookies by contacting us at info@cagewarriors.com or visit
www.allaboutcookies.org.
How we use cookies on our Website and what information we collect
Session cookies
      •  To allow you to carry information across pages of our site and avoid having to sign in
         many times.
Persistent cookies:
      •  To help us recognise you as a unique visitor (a number) when you return to the
         Website and to allow us to tailor content to match your preferred interests.
      •  To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users
         use the Website and to help us improve the structure of the Website. We cannot
         identify you personally in this way.

Please note that we use Google Analytics to collect information about you in aggregated
form to help CW understand how the Website is being use and to help CW customise the
Website for you. For more information about Google’s privacy policy, please visit
http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/. If you do not wish to allow the use of Google
Analytics cookies at all, Google provides an opt-out plug-in for most common website
browsers http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Disabling or enabling cookies
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser.
However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our Website if cookies
are disabled.
As noted in ‘Links to third party sites’, we may provide options to share content on social
media which may result in your being directed to the social media network’s own systems. If
you proceed with this, those networks may gather personal data about you in line with their
own privacy policies.
    8. Your Rights
As a data subject you have a number of rights in relation to your personal data. Below, we
have described the various rights that you have, as well as how you can exercise them.
Right of Access
You may, at any time, request access to the personal data that we hold which relates to you
(you may have heard of this right being described as a "subject access request").
Please note that this right entitles you to receive a copy of the personal data that we hold
about you in order to enable you to check that it is correct and to ensure that we are
processing that personal data lawfully. It is not a right that allows you to request personal
data about other people, or a right to request specific documents from us that do not relate
to your personal data.
You can exercise this right at any time by writing to us using the contact details set out here
and telling us that you are making a subject access request. You do not have to fill in a
specific form to make this kind of request.
Your Right to Rectification and Erasure
You may, at any time, request that we correct personal data that we hold about you which
you believe is incorrect or inaccurate. You may also ask us to erase personal data if you do
not believe that we need to continue retaining it (you may have heard of this right described
as the “right to be forgotten”).
Please note that we may ask you to verify any new data that you provide to us and may take
our own steps to check that the new data you have supplied us with is right. Further, we are
not always obliged to erase personal data when asked to do so; if for any reason we believe

that we have a good legal reason to continue processing personal data that you ask us to
erase we will tell you what that reason is at the time we respond to your request.
You can exercise this right at any time by writing to us using the contact details set out here
and telling us that you are making a request to have your personal data rectified or erased
and on what basis you are making that request. If you want us to replace inaccurate data
with new data, you should tell us what that new data is. You do not have to fill in a specific
form to make this kind of request.
Your Right to Restrict Processing
Where we process your personal data on the basis of a legitimate interest (see the section of
this Policy which explains why we use your personal data) you are entitled to ask us to stop
processing it in that way if you feel that our continuing to do so impacts on your fundamental
rights and freedoms or if you feel that those legitimate interests are not valid.
You may also ask us to stop processing your personal data: (a) if you dispute the accuracy
of that personal data and want us verify that data's accuracy; (b) where it has been
established that our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where
we no longer need to process your personal data (and would otherwise dispose of it) but you
wish for us to continue storing it in order to enable you to establish, exercise or defend legal
claims.
Please note that if for any reason we believe that we have a good legal reason to continue
processing personal data that you ask us to stop processing, we will tell you what that
reason is, either at the time we first respond to your request or after we have had the
opportunity to consider and investigate it.
You can exercise this right at any time by writing to us using the contact details set out here
and telling us that you are making a request to have us stop processing the relevant aspect
of your personal data and describing which of the above conditions you believe is relevant to
that request. You do not have to fill in a specific form to make this kind of request.
Your Right to Portability
Where you wish to transfer certain personal data that we hold about you, which is processed
by automated means, to a third party you may write to us and ask us to provide it to you in a
commonly used machine-readable format.
Because of the kind of work that we do and the systems that we use, we do not envisage
this right being particularly relevant to the majority of individuals with whom we interact.
However, if you wish to transfer your data from us to a third party we are happy to consider
such requests.
Your Right to stop receiving communications
For details on your rights to ask us to stop sending you various kinds of communications,
please contact us.
Your Right to object to automated decision making and profiling

You have the right to be informed about the existence of any automated decision making
and profiling of your personal data, and where appropriate, be provided with meaningful
information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and the envisaged
consequences of such processing that affects you.
Exercising your rights
When you write to us making a request to exercise your rights we are entitled to ask you to
prove that you are who you say you are. We may ask you to provide copies of relevant ID
documents to help us to verify your identity.
It will help us to process your request if you clearly state which right you wish to exercise
and, where relevant, why it is that you are exercising it. The clearer and more specific you
can be the faster and more efficiently we can deal with your request. If you do not provide us
with sufficient information then we may delay actioning your request until you have provided
us with additional information (and where this is the case we will tell you).
For our contact details, please see here.
    9. Contact Details
If you have any queries regarding this Policy, or if you think that it has not been followed,
please contact: info@cagewarriors.com
